Zeynep Gök

Website: zeynepgok.me

Email: zeynep.gk3@gmail.com

LinkedIn: zeynepgok

GitHub: github.com/zeynepgk3



SUMMARY

I am interested in any projects related to software engineering. I want to experience various positions in my junior years and choose one i like most as my main profession. Currently focused on my graduation project on computer vision.

EDUCATION

Istanbul University Cerrahpasa

Bachelor of Computer Engineering, 4th Grade

Istanbul, TR 2017–Present

EXPERIENCE

PIA Bilisim Istanbul

Junior Software Developer

Mar 2021 - current

- We are using various technologies such as; Spring Boot, MongoDB, Postgresql, Camunda, Kafka etc.

ISTEC Istanbul

Web Application Security Intern

Jul 2021 - Oct 2021

- LetMeHack is a cyber security training platform, which users can test their hacking skills with pre-prepared laboratories we have created.
- These labs contains various vulnerabilities like xss, sql injection, file injection, command execution vs.
- We created multiple lab containers that can be opened and closed by one main container, using Docker.
- With Scrum methodology, we managed to organise our team work.
- Beside below, I also developed main website's front-end and back-end with PHP.

Cheefim Istanbul

Junior Full Stack Developer

Feb - May 2021

- Studied React, React Native and solved current mobile application's UI issues
- Developed front-end using Angular.js framework

Infotech Academy

Istanbul

Jul - Aug 2020

- Unicourses is an online course platform; which users can sell their courses depends their skills and knowledge, buy and view other users's courses.
- Used .NET Core and MVC design pattern.
- Lead my team as a Scrum Master

IQ Eğitim

Istanbul

Primary School Tutor

Nov 2018 - Sep 2019

GameEkstra

Istanbul Mar - Sep 2018 Designer

SKILLS LANGUAGES

• Programming: Java, JavaScript, C#, Dart

• Database: SQL, PostgreSQL

Web/Mobile: Angular, Flutter, React Native, Bootstrap, Spring Boot

• Design: XD, Photoshop, Illustrator

• English: Intermediate

• Spanish: Elementary

• Turkish: Native

ACTIVITIES

• Chairwoman of IUC Bilgisayar Kulübü Sep 2019 - Sep 2020 Organizing events, finding mentors and sponsors for projects, design and media management, etc.

• IEEE Member 2017 - Sep 2019 Medya ve Sponsorluk, Computer Society

Courses

• PIA Group Winter Camp Feb 2021 In a week; we have been taught Project Management, Analysis, Testing, DevOps Engineering, Spring Boot and Microservices, Angular.js, MongoDB, SQL, Camunda, Kafka and Git in a basic way. The next week, we were separated groups and developed our own project called MyBuddy using these technologies.

• BLL CCNA1 | Cisco Academy Feb 2020

• GNU/LINUX System Management 1.5 | Mustafa Akgul Free Software Winter Camp Jan 2020

• GNU/LINUX System Management 1.0 | Mustafa Akgul Free Software Summer Camp Jul - Aug 2019

• Introduction To Cyber Security | | Cisco Academy May 2019

• Introduction to Wireless Networking | Cisco Academy May 2019

Page 2 of 2